こちらです
Over here.
What's this?
こいつは
All of you, return to your posts.
お前たちは持ち場へ戻れ
It looks like a ball of mercury.
水銀の滴みたいに見えますね
It's like it's alive.
まるで生きているようだな
I have to move this out of here...
こいつは運び出さないと　こいつは運び出さないと
Is something wrong?
どうかしましたか
こいつは運び出さないと
Load it on the truck!
トラックに乗せるんだ
Quickly!
急げ
Utw
Presents
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
今聖杯戦争は重大な危機に見舞われている
The Holy Grail War is in grave peril.
It is confirmed that Caster's Master is behind
the kidnappings tormenting Fuyuki City as of late.
キャスターのマスターは昨今の冬木市を騒がせている
連続誘拐事件の犯人であることが判明した
Therefore, I will make use of my emergency powers as judge and temporarily alter the rules of the Grail War.
よって私は非常時における監督権限をここに発動し
暫定的ルール変更を設定する
すべてのマスターは直ちに互いの戦闘行動を中断し
All Masters are to immediately cease any ongoing
combat and focus on exterminating Caster instead.
各々　キャスター殲滅に尽力せよ
The one who defeats Caster and his Master will
receive an additional Command Spell as a reward.
そして見事キャスターとそのマスターを討ち取った者には
特例措置として追加の令呪を寄贈する
これは過去の聖杯戦争で脱落したマスターたちが使い残した令呪である
These are unused Command Spells the fallen Masters of past Grail Wars have left behind.
They should be of immeasurable value to you all.
諸君らにとって　これらの刻印は貴重きわまりない価値を持つはずだ
Once it is proven that Caster has been
exterminated, the Grail War will resume as usual.
キャスターの消滅が確認された時点で
改めて聖杯戦争を再開するものとする
If anyone has questions, now is the time to ask them.
さて　質問がある者は今この場で申し出るがいい
もっとも　人語を発音できる者のみに限らせてもらうがね
Though, that would be limited to speakers of the human tongue.
Well done, priest.
お見事でした　神父
Now all the Masters will hunt him down.
これでマスターたちは狐狩りに興じることになるでしよう
教会に集まった使い魔は五体でした
Five familiars were gathered at the church.
Which means...
つまり
Which means that Lord El-Melloi survived.
つまり生死不明であったロード·エルメロイも生きているというわけですね
Indeed.
いかにも
And with a Command Spell as the reward,
そうして令呪という報酬であれば
Lord El-Melloi, having already used one, won't let this
opportunity pass by. Neither will the other Masters.
既に一角を消費しているロード·エルメロイは勿論
他のマスターたちも動かざるを得ないでしよう
They'll want to keep it from the rest...
他者が追加令呪を手に入れないよう
そして自らが追加令呪を独占できるように
...by claiming it for themselves.
But that also means the Master who obtains the
Command Spell will gain a formidable advantage.
しかし　それだけに令呪を手に入れたマスターには
大きなアドバンテージが齎されるでしょう
Of course, that wouldn't be good.
無論　それは好ましくない
Once Caster is weakened from being hunted by the others...
他の猟犬たちに追いつめられ衰弱し切ったキャスターにとどめを刺すのは
...Archer'll be the one to finish him off.
やはり　アーチャーでなければなりますまい
U-Um...
あ　あの
こちらはマッケンジー様のお宅で宜しいでしょうか
Is this the Mackenzie residence?
うむ　それはここの家主の姓で相違ない
Yes, that is the name of this house's owner.
ええと 征服王イスカンダル様っていらっしゃいますか
Well then...
Is Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors, at home?
余のことだが
That would be me.
Oh, I see.
ああ はい そうでしたか
あ ここに受け取りのサインを　お願いします
Um, could you please sign on the receipt here?
My signature? Very well!
署名か　宜しい
You have my thanks.
確かに受け取ったぞ
Th-Thank you for your patronage...
ま　毎度ありがとうございました
Rider's Admirable Shirt:    War Tactics
この胸板に世界全図を載せるとは
It feels good to have the entire world mapped across my chest!
実に小気味良い
Why are you dressed like that?
どうしたんだ　その格好
My package just arrived.
荷物が届いたんでな
You went outside?!
お前外へ出たのか
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Tada!
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
通信販売とやらを試してみたのだ
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
I tried this "ordering by post" thing.
Receiver
Sender
Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors
Mackenzie Residence
Nakagoe 2-2-8
Fuyuki City Miyama District
Miturin Netshop
Honmachi 2-15-1
Mifune City
Type:
Address:
Name:
Clothing
Delivery
Express
お前　二階から出るなって言ったろう
I told you not to leave the second floor!
If the occupants aren't home and you're busy
with your familiar, who else can answer the door?
家主も外出中　貴様も使い魔にかまけているとなれば
余が代りに出るしかなかろう
I had no choice.
仕方ないだろう
It's rare to be summoned by the Church.
聖堂教会から呼び出しなんて
異例なんだから
Don't be so grouchy.
ま　いいではないか
I came to a realization after seeing Saber last night.
昨夜のセイバーを見てな　余もひらめいたのだ
If I wear modern attire, there should be no
problems with going outside in corporeal form.
当代風の衣装を着れば
実体化したまま街を出歩いたって文句はあるまい
Hey, wait!
おい　待て
At least put some pants on before you go out!
外に出る前にズボンくらい履け
Oh, leggings.
ああ　脚絆か
That's right, everyone in this country wears them.
そういえば　この国では皆が履いておったな
ありゃあ必須か
Do I have to?
Of course you do!
必要不可欠だ
And before you ask, I'm definitely not going
all the way to town just to buy you XL pants.
先に断っておくが
僕はお前のために街まで出向いて特大ズボンを買ってくるなんてことは絶対しないからな
なんだとう
What?!
Boy, are you opposing my authority?!
坊主　貴様　余の覇道に異を唱えると申すか
Authority and your pants have zilch, zero, and absolutely nothing to do with one another!
覇道とオマエのズボンとは一切合切　金輪際まったくもって関係ない
Go defeat an enemy Servant before you start thinking about screwing around outside!
外を遊び歩く算段なんぞする前に
敵のサーヴァントの一人でも討ち取ってみろ
Then I'll buy you pants or whatever you want.
そしたらズボンでも何でも買ってやる
I understand.
なるほど　あいわかった
Very well.
So you swear that you'll buy me pants once I've defeated an enemy Servant?
とりあえず敵の御首級を上げさえすれば
その時は余にズボンを履かすと誓うわけだな
お前
You...
そんなに現代の格好で外を出歩きたいのか
Do you really want to walk around
outside in modern clothes that much?
The King of Knights was doing it.
騎士王の奴めがやっておったのだ
As a fellow king, I cannot allow myself to be left behind.
余も王として遅れを取るわけにはいかん
I like the design on this shirt.
この服の柄は気に入った
It's a fitting shirt for a ruler!
覇者の装束に相応しい
キャスターの居所を突き止めなきゃいけないってのに
Even though it's important that we find where Caster is...
What are we doing?
何やってんだ
There is a powerful field over Mt. Enzou, with Ryuudou Temple as its origin.
円蔵山には柳洞寺を基点として強力な結界が張られている
そのせいでサーヴァントのような自然霊以外の存在は参道からしか進入できない
Because of that, anything that isn't a natural spirit,
such as a Servant, can only enter via the temple path.
セイバーを使う上では留意しておいてくれ
Bear that in mind when using Saber.
There are three other spots where the ley lines converge.
地脈の集中する要地があと三つ
Tohsaka Manor, Fuyuki Church, and...
遠坂邸と冬木教会　それに都市区画の東にある新興住宅地がそれだ
New Town, East
...this new residential area east of the city center.
Consequently, this means there
are four locations in Fuyuki City...
よって　聖杯の降霊を行えるだけの霊格を備えたポイントは
...that have all the spiritual characteristics needed for the Grail to appear.
冬木市内に都合四カ所あることになる
When the war enters its second phase and the Servants are narrowed down,
戦いの後半　サーヴァントの数が絞り込まれてきたら
we'll have to secure one of these
as our base of operations, won't we?
このいずれかを拠点として制圧しておかなくてはいけないわけね
That's right.
そういうことだ
That covers the lay of the land.
地勢についてはこんなところだが　何か質問は
Any questions?
何か不明な点はある
Is there anything you aren't clear on?
これといって特には　充分な説明でした
Not particularly.
It was a perfectly adequate explanation.
切嗣　他のマスターも全員がキャスターを狙うと見ていいかしら
Kiritsugu, can we assume all the other Masters will go for Caster?
間違いないだろうね
No doubt about that.
だがキャスターに関しては　僕らにアドバンテージがある
But we have the advantage with regards to Caster.
何を血迷ったか
Out of whatever madness, he believes Saber to be Jeanne d'Arc, which is to our benefit.
セイバーをジャンヌ·ダルクと勘違いして付け狙っているんだから
こいつは好都合だ
僕らは待ち構えているだけでいい
We just need to wait for him to come.
マスター　それでは足りない
Master, that won't be enough.
奴の悪行は容認しがたい
His evil deeds cannot be tolerated.
We should go after him before the damage spreads further.
これ以上被害が拡がる前にこちらから討って出るべきです
アイリ　この森の結界の術式はもう把握できたかい
Iri, have you grasped control of
the spells of the fields in this forest?
Yes, I have.
ええ　大丈夫
それよりも問題はセイバーの左手の呪いよ
But our real problem is the curse on Saber's left arm.
あなたがケイネスを仕留めて十八時間経つけれど
Eighteen hours have passed since you
defeated Kayneth, but Saber's arm won't heal.
セイバーの腕は完治しないままよ
ランサーはまだ健在なんだわ
Lancer must still be alive.
Shouldn't we defeat Lancer first, so we can face Caster at full strength?
キャスターを万全の態勢で迎撃するためにも
まずはランサーを倒すべきじゃないかしら
That's unnecessary.
それには及ばない
君は地の利を最大限に活かしてセイバーを逃げ回らせ
Just use your knowledge of the area to confuse the enemy and keep Saber away from him.
敵を撹乱してくれればいい
You won't have her fight Caster?
キャスターと戦わせないの
キャスターは放っておいても誰かが仕留めるさ
Someone else will deal with him anyway.
In fact, the ones going after Caster
frenziedly would make much better targets.
むしろキャスターを追って血眼になっている連中こそ
格好の獲物なんだよ
I'll attack from the side and defeat them.
僕はそいつらを側面から襲って叩く
Master, just...
マスター　貴方という人は
いったいどこまで卑劣に成り果てる気だ
Just how despicable can you get?!
You mock us Heroic Spirits.
貴方は英霊を侮辱している
Why won't you let me fight?
なぜ戦いを私に委ねてくれない
Are you saying that you can't trust me, your own Servant?!
貴方は自身のサーヴァントである私を信用できないというのか
The new rule says we can't fight anyone but Caster, right?
キャスター以外とは休戦のはずでしょ
構わないよ
It doesn't matter.
I just can't trust the judge of this war.
今回の監督役はどうにも信用できない
He feigns ignorance while sheltering Assassin's Master.
なにせ素知らぬ顔でアサシンのマスターを匿っている奴だ
He might also be working with Tohsaka.
遠坂ともグルかもしれない
We'd do well to be wary of him.
疑ってかかった方がいいだろ
That will be all.
それじゃあ　解散としよう
Kiritsugu...
切嗣
If...
もし
もし僕が
If I...
If I decided to just abandon everything and run away right now...
僕が今ここで何もかも放り投げて逃げ出すと決めたら
Iri, would you come with me?
アイリ　君は一緒に来てくれるか
イリヤは　城にいるあの子はどうするの
What about Ilya?
The girl's still in the castle!
I'll go back and pick her up, killing anyone in the way.
戻って連れ出す　邪魔する奴は殺す
And then...
それから先は
I'll devote everything I have to just you and Ilya!
僕は僕の全てを君とイリヤのためだけに費やす
Can we really run away?
逃げられるの　私たち
We can!
逃げられる　今ならば　まだ
If we run now, we can still...
嘘
Lies.
That's a lie.
それは嘘よ
あなたは決して逃げられない
You could never run away.
You would never forgive yourself for abandoning the Grail and failing to save the world.
聖杯を捨てた自分を　世界を救えなかった自分を
あなたは決して赦せない
As your own first and final accuser, you would end your own life.
きっとあなた自身が　最初で最後の断罪者として
衛宮切嗣を殺してしまう
I'm scared.
怖いんだ
He...
奴が
言峰綺礼が僕を狙っている
Kotomine Kirei is after me.
Maiya told me.
舞弥に聞いた
He used Kayneth as a bait to draw me out.
奴は僕を吊る餌としてケイネスを張っていた
He anticipated my actions.
行動を読まれていた
君を犠牲にして戦うのに
I'm already sacrificing you to fight, and I had to leave Ilya behind...
イリヤを残したままなのに
But the most dangerous of them has already decided to pursue me.
一番危険な奴がもう僕に狙いを定めている
The one enemy I didn't want to face!
決して遭いたくなかったアイツが
I won't let you fight alone.
あなた一人を戦わせはしない
I'll protect you.
私が守る　セイバーが守る
Saber will protect you.
And... you also have Maiya-san.
それに
舞弥さんもいる
切嗣
Kiritsugu?
An enemy attack?
敵襲か
I'm glad Maiya didn't leave yet.
舞弥が発つ前で幸いだった
今なら総出で迎撃できる
We can mount an attack together.
アイリ　遠見の水晶球を用意してくれ
Iri, prepare a remote-viewing crystal ball.
いたわ
There they are.
Irisviel, the enemy is provoking us.
アイリスフィール　敵は誘いをかけています
They must be hostages.
人質でしょうね　きっと
I'll have to go down and save them.
私が直に出向いて救い出すしかありません
千里眼を見破られてる
He knows we're watching him!
As promised last night, I, Gilles de Rais, have come.
昨夜の約定通り
ジル·ド·レェ罷り越してございます
I would like an audience with Jeanne, my beautiful Holy Virgin.
我が麗しの聖処女ジャンヌに　今一度　お目通りを願いたい
Irisviel!
アイリスフィール
Feel free to take your time.
取り次ぎはごゆるりと
I have come prepared for a lengthy wait.
私も気長に待たせていただくつもりで それなりの準備をして参りましたからね
さあさあ　坊やたち　鬼ごっこを始めますよ
Now, children, it's time to play tag.
The rules are simple: you just need to run away from me.
ルールは簡単　この私から逃げ切ればいいのです
If you can't...
さもなくば
Stop!
やめろ
Now, run!
さあ　お逃げなさい　百を数えたら追いかけますよ
I'll come after you once I've counted up to a hundred.
Well, Jeanne?
ジャンヌ
How long do you think it'll take me to catch them all?
私が全員捕まえるまでにどのぐらいかかりますかね
Saber, defeat Caster!
セイバー　キャスターを倒して
I shall!
はい
Welcome, Jeanne.
ようこそ　ジャンヌ
How do you like this terrible spectacle?
如何ですか　この惨状は
It pains you, doesn't it?
痛ましいでしょう
Do you hate me?
私が憎いですか
え 憎いでしょうともねえ
I'm sure you do.
I'm sure you'd never forgive me for turning away from God's love.
神の愛に背いた私を断じて赦せないはずだ
Let the child go, fiend!
その子を放せ 外道
Jeanne, since you wish to rescue him that badly...
ジャンヌ 貴女がそんなにもこの子の救命を望むなら
さあ坊や  お喜びなさい
Okay, boy.
Rejoice.
It appears a devout messenger of God has come to save you.
敬虔なる神の使いが君を助けてくれるそうだ
It's dangerous here.
ここは危険だ
さあ 早く逃げなさい
Now, run away from here.
Follow the path, and you'll reach a large castle.
このまま進めば大きな城がある
I told you!
申し上げたはずですよ
That I would come well-prepared the next time we meet.
次に会うときは相応の準備をしてくると
Very well.
良いだろう もはや貴様と聖杯を競おうとは思わない
I won't think to fight you for the Grail any longer!
Oh, Jeanne...
おおお ジャンヌ
なんと気高い なんと雄々しい
How noble! How valiant!
ああ聖処女よ  貴女の前には神すら霞む
O Holy Virgin, your presence dulls even that of God!
Caster!
キャスター　私は貴様を滅ぼすためだけに剣を執る
I take up my sword only to destroy you!
If only I could use my left hand...
左手さえ使えれば
There should be a limit to Caster's mana.
キャスターの魔力だって無限じゃないはず
枯渇するまで持ちこたえれば　セイバーに勝機があるわよね
If Saber can last until it runs out, she can win, right?
Kiritsugu?
切嗣
More importantly, is there still no sign that other Masters have entered the forest?
それより まだ他のマスターが森に入ってきた反応はないのか
Maiya.
舞弥 アイリを連れて城から逃げてくれ
Take Iri and run from the castle.
Head in the opposite direction from Saber and Caster.
セイバーたちとは逆方向に
I can't stay here?
ここにいては 駄目なの
This isn't a safe place with Saber fighting elsewhere.
セイバーが離れた場所で戦っている以上安全ではない
I'm sure someone else also arrived at the same conclusion.
僕と同じことを考えている奴だっているだろうからね
All right.
わかったわ
どうした アイリ
What's wrong, Iri?
Looks like another has arrived.
どうやら新手がやってきたみたい
How come?
なぜだ
Is there no end to his mana?
奴の魔力は底なしだというのか
No...
まさか 奴の魔力の源は
Could the source of his mana be...
So that book is your Noble Phantasm?
その本が貴様の宝具か
Yes.
ええ 我が盟友プレラーティの遺した魔書により
I learned how to command a demonic legion from the grimoire my sworn friend Prelati left behind.
私は悪魔の軍勢を従える術を得たのです
What do you think, Jeanne?
如何です　ジャンヌ
Doesn't it bring back memories, Jeanne?
懐かしいですね　ジャンヌ
Everything is just as it was back then.
何もかも昔のままだ
Your noble vigor and dignified air all prove you to be Jeanne d'Arc without a doubt!
その気高き闘志 尊き魂の在りようは
紛れもなく貴女がジャンヌ·ダルクであることの証
So why?!
それなのに なぜだ
Why won't you awaken?
なぜ目覚めてくれないのです
Do you still believe in God's grace?
未だ神のご加護を信じておいでか
この窮地にも奇跡が貴女を救うと
You still think a miracle will save you from this predicament?
How tragic!
嘆かわしい
Have you forgotten the Battle of Compiègne?
コンピエーニュの戦いをお忘れか
Despite all the humiliation you suffered,
you're still content with being a puppet of God?!
あれほどの辱めを受けてなお
貴女は神の操り人形に甘んじるのか
無様だぞ　セイバー
How disappointing, Saber.
That swordsmanship was far from captivating enough to do the King of Knights justice.
もっと魅せる剣でなければ騎士王の名が泣くではないか
Who are you?!
何者だ  誰の赦しを得てこの私を邪魔立てするか
Who gave you permission to interfere?!
それはこちらの台詞だ 外道
That's my question, fiend.
It will be my spear that takes Saber's life!
セイバーの首級は我が槍の勲
My prayers, my Holy Grail brought that woman back to life!
私の祈りが 私の聖杯が
その女性を蘇らせたのだ
She belongs to me.
彼女は私のものだ
Every ounce of flesh, every drop of blood...
肉の一片から血の一滴まで
Even her soul itself is mine!
その魂に至るまで私のものだ
なあ キャスター
Hey, Caster.
I won't be meddling in your love affair.
べつに俺は貴様の恋路にまで口出しはせんよ
是が非でもセイバーを屈服させて奪いたいというのなら
If you're set on subjugating Saber and making
her yours no matter what, then go ahead and try.
やってみればいいさ
However...
ただし
I won't allow you to defeat Saber,
who has lost an arm, in my presence!
このディルムッドを差し置いて
片腕のみのセイバーを討ち果たすことだけは断じて
許さん
Lancer, you...
ランサー 貴方
Don't get me wrong, Saber.
勘違いするなよ セイバー
The only order I was given today was to defeat Caster.
今日の俺が仰せつかったのは
キャスターを倒せという命令のみだ
Thus, I believe cooperation to be our best option here.
ならばここは共闘が最善と判断するが
どうだ
Well?
断っておくが  ランサー
Just to be clear, Lancer.
I could kill a hundred of those things with just one arm.
私なら 左手一本であの雑魚どもを100は潰すぞ
That number is nothing to speak of.
その程度なら造作もない
U-Unforgivable...
許さぬ
思い上がるなよ　この匹夫めが
Don't get carried away, you bastard!
Fervor, mei sanguis.
Boil, my blood.
沸き立て 我が血潮
アーチボルト家九代目当主
I, the ninth head of the Archibald
family, Kayneth El-Melloi, have come.
ケイネス·エルメロイがここに仕る
Einzbern Mage, let us duel for the
Grail with our lives and our honor!
アインツベルンの魔術師よ
求める聖杯に命と誇りを賭して
いざ尋常に立ち会うがいい
You rely on traps?
からくり仕掛け頼みとは
Have you really fallen so low, Einzbern?
ここまで堕ちたか  アインツベルン
Very well.
よろしい ならばこれは決闘ではなく誅伐だ
This is no longer a duel, but an extermination!
I see.
なるほど
Automatic Searching.
自動索敵か
Found you, rat.
見つけたぞ ネズミめが
Scalp!
Strike!
斬
Time Alter: Double Accel!
固有時制御 二倍速
自らの体内を固有結界として 時間を操り加速したというところか
You created a Reality Marble in your
own body to control time and accelerate.
Looks like you do know a little magic.
少しは魔術の心得もあるわけだな
But only a coward would rely on such petty tricks after having been trained as a Mage.
仮にも魔術の薫陶を受けながら
下賎な小細工に頼る卑劣漢め
Die and realize your place.
死んで身の程を弁えるのだな
Ire Sanctio!
Track and kill!
追跡抹殺
Controlling time within himself must place great stress on his body.
体内時間を操るとなれば 肉体にかかる負担も相当なものだ
Found him.
見つけたか
Now, how far can you run in that physical condition?
さて その体でどこまで逃げきれるかな
Time Alter: Triple Stagnate.
固有時制御 二倍速
This thing doesn't have eyes to see with.
コイツは目が見えているわけじゃない
If I slow my internal time to a third of its original, and
my heart rate and breathing rate as much as possible...
体内時間を三分の一まで遅らせて  心拍を呼吸を限界まで抑えれば
It won't be able to detect me.
対象を感知できない
Kayneth!
ケイネス
Fool! It's useless!
馬鹿めが  無駄な足掻きだ
Episode 7
Forest of Demons
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
Maiya-san, no!
舞弥さん 駄目
He's a disgrace to Magi everywhere.
魔術師の面汚しが
Tremble and fall into despair.
恐怖なさい 絶望なさい
Pierce it, Gae Dearg!
抉れ 破魔の紅薔薇
On whose will did the both of you fight?
おまえたちは誰の意志で戦った
Prepare to die, fiend.
覚悟はいいな　外道
Next Episode
Mage Killer